<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>July</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Better Home</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 03:12:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/creative-home-decor-logo-detailing-260nw-716262226.jpg</url>
	<title>July</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>5 Plants best for our health</title>
		<link>/2024/06/19/107/</link>
					<comments>/2024/06/19/107/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cloud1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 02:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Plants]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=107</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What are the plants best for our health? The healthiest houseplant is the one that matches your personal style as well as daily schedule and routine, says Alex Cromer, LPC, a licensed professional mental health counselor with Thriveworks in Richmond, Virginia. And, don’t worry too much if you don’t have a green thumb! Many of the best plants for your health...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<em><strong>What are the plants best for our health?</strong></em> The healthiest houseplant is the one that matches your personal style as well as daily schedule and routine, says <strong><a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/therapists/alexandra-cromer-richmond-va/853300" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Alex Cromer, LPC</a></strong>, a licensed professional mental health counselor with <a href="https://thriveworks.com/richmond-therapy/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Thriveworks</a> in Richmond, Virginia. And, don’t worry<em> too much</em> if you <a href="https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/home/gardening/advice/g1285/hard-to-kill-plants/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">don’t have a green thumb</a>! Many of the best plants for your health are easy to care for, so you can enjoy their presence and reap the health rewards.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:image {"id":35,"width":"456px","height":"auto","sizeSlug":"full","linkDestination":"none","align":"left"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image alignleft size-full is-resized"><a href="/spider-plant/" data-wplink-url-error="true"><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-35" style="width: 456px; height: auto;" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/spider-plant-home-decoration.jpg" alt="plants best for our health" width="980" height="976" /></a></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><a href="/spider-plant/" data-wplink-url-error="true">1.Spider Plant</a></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

Spider plants, or <em>Chlorophytum comosum</em>, <a href="https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/home/gardening/a40364368/spider-plant-care" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">are extremely easy to grow</a>, don’t require constant attention and thrive with little investment on your behalf. The plants have narrow leaves and get their name from the “small plantlets produced on long trailing stems that vaguely resemble spiders,” according to the <a href="https://hort.extension.wisc.edu/articles/spider-plant-chlorophytum-comosum/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">University of Wisconsin-Madison Division of Extension</a>.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

Spider are plants  best for our health because it  helps to purify the surrounding air. <a href="https://ntrs.nasa.gov/citations/19930073077" target="_blank" rel="noopener">NASA research</a> examined the leaves, soil, roots and microorganisms of several houseplants and found that plants can act as a natural air filter to reduce pollutants. The study indicates that spider plants removed 95% of toxic formaldehyde from the air in a sealed Plexiglas container over a 24-hour period.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:image {"id":36,"width":"300px","height":"auto","sizeSlug":"full","linkDestination":"none","align":"right"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image alignright size-full is-resized"></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">2.Peace Lily</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

The name “peace lily” definitely evokes a sense of calm. These sturdy plants also “flower and are aesthetically pleasing” and may be  best for our health over time, explains <strong><a href="https://thespadr.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Trevor Cates, N.D</a>,</strong> a naturopathic doctor in Park City, Utah, and author of <a href="https://www.amazon.com/Clean-Skin-Within-Two-Week-Naturally/dp/1592337430/ref=tmm_pap_swatch_0?ots=1&amp;_encoding=UTF8&amp;qid=1539230711&amp;sr=8-1&amp;linkCode=ogi&amp;tag=goodhousekeeping_auto-append-20&amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.g.40742429%5Bsrc%7Cwww.google.com%5Bch%7C%5Blt%7C%5Bpid%7C12319752-89b0-49de-aced-029e619e179b%5Baxid%7C81a03166-0678-4e97-a94d-00747b6dab29" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Clean Skin From Within</em></a>. A 2022 study published in <a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3417/12/1/284/htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Applied Sciences</em></a> suggests that peace lilies have air-cleaning properties and <a href="https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/home/a36386047/what-is-carbon-footprint/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">help to remove carbon dioxide</a> and <a href="https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/home/g2120/indoor-air-quality-47020101/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">volatile organic compounds (VOCs) from the air</a>.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

Peace lilies can live for years and continuously produce broad white flowers that resemble a white peace flag, per materials published by <a href="https://www.miraclegro.com/en-us/library/indoor-gardening/how-grow-peace-lilies" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">MiracleGro</a>. They’re easy to take care of and don’t need much light, so they’re perfect for shady spaces. Just keep them <a href="https://www.goodhousekeeping.com/home/gardening/advice/g1174/deadly-poisonous-plants/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">out of reach from pets and small children</a>, as they can cause vomiting or tongue swelling if they’re ingested.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:media-text {"mediaId":37,"mediaLink":"/home/ficus-elastic-plant-rubber-tree/","mediaType":"image"} -->
<div class="wp-block-media-text is-stacked-on-mobile">
<figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-37 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/ficus-elastic-plant-rubber-tree.jpg" alt="plants best for our health" width="980" height="978" /></figure>
<div class="wp-block-media-text__content"><!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">3.Rubber Plants</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->Rubber plants — also known as rubber trees or <em>Ficus elastica </em>— make for great indoor houseplants which are plants best for our health. They’re generally easy to take care of and only need to be watered every week or so, according to materials shared by <a href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=74968X1525078&amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.thesill.com%2Fblog%2Fhow-to-care-for-rubber-tree-ficus-elastica&amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goodhousekeeping.com%2Fhome%2Fgardening%2Fg40742429%2Fbest-indoor-plants-for-health%2F&amp;xs=1&amp;xcust=%5Butm_source%7C%5Butm_campaign%7C%5Butm_medium%7C%5Bgclid%7C%5Bmsclkid%7C%5Bfbclid%7C%5Brefdomain%7Cwww.google.com%5Bcontent_id%7C1288bee8-21a8-43bb-a541-342ef44d238e%5Bcontent_product_id%7Ce047435f-2092-49c5-8a77-842b6d8b7adb%5Bproduct_retailer_id%7C29b65fa2-9e25-4546-944d-4d69d53b1df7%5Blt%7Csale%5Baxid%7C163aa6f5-06f7-4bb5-9a6a-d47d92ac628f%5Boptxid%7C%5Boptvid%7C" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">The Sill</a>. Research shows that rubber plants feature air-purifying properties. Just be sure to keep them firmly away from any pets and from young children, as they&#8217;re known to be highly toxic when ingested. <!-- /wp:paragraph -->

</div>
</div>
<!-- /wp:media-text -->

<!-- wp:media-text {"mediaPosition":"right","mediaId":38,"mediaLink":"/home/alocasia-sanderiana/","mediaType":"image"} -->
<div class="wp-block-media-text has-media-on-the-right is-stacked-on-mobile">
<div class="wp-block-media-text__content">
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">4.Elephant Ear Plants</h2>
If you want to spend a <em>little</em> more time with your houseplants, Cromer recommends elephant ear plants. These are organized into a group of tropical, perennial plants instantly recognizable by their big, heart-shaped leaves.

They need bright light and regular watering to keep the soil moist, and they can get big and may need extra space. Some species  which are a food staple in certain tropical regions. Medicinally, the leaves have been noted to be plants best for our health.

</div>
<figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-38 size-full" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/alocasia-sanderiana.jpg" alt="plants best for our health" width="980" height="981" /></figure>
</div>
<!-- wp:heading {"textAlign":"center"} -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center">5.Golden Pothos</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:image {"width":"535px","height":"auto","align":"left"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image alignleft is-resized"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone" style="width: 535px; height: auto;" src="https://images.everydayhealth.com/images/wellness/houseplants-that-are-good-for-your-health-02-golden-pothos-1440x810.jpg?w=768" alt="plants best for our health" width="768" height="432" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

Another easy-to-care-for plant, the golden pothos (<em>Epipremnum aureum</em>) doesn’t just look pretty, with its vines and heart-shaped leaves: It’s also known for being a natural air purifier. For example, one <a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0360132317301592" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">study</a> suggested that golden pothos can effectively lower indoor ozone levels. And other <a href="https://ntrs.nasa.gov/citations/20160005687" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">research</a> on the air-purifying benefits of plants showed that, like the peace lily, the golden pothos plant can remove VOCs from the air.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

Keep in mind that, also like the peace lily, the golden pothos contains oxalate, which the notes can be harmful to your pets if ingested.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->

<strong>How to Care for Them</strong> This low-maintenance plant is also a good choice for people who may have erratic watering habits. Just take care to not over water them.

<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/06/19/107/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bunny Tails</title>
		<link>/2024/06/17/bunny-tails/</link>
					<comments>/2024/06/17/bunny-tails/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cloud1]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Bunny tails]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Bunny Tials New]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=64</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[&#8220;Bunny tails&#8221; typically refer to a type of ornamental grass known scientifically as Lagurus ovatus. These charming plants are native to the Mediterranean region and are widely cultivated for their fluffy, soft flower heads that resemble the tails of rabbits, hence the name &#8220;bunny tails.&#8221; Here are some key points about bunny tails: Overall, bunny...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="wp-block-image">
<figure class="alignright size-full is-resized"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="4480" height="6720" src="/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/bunny.jpeg" alt="bunny tails" class="wp-image-204" style="width:337px;height:auto"/></figure></div>


<p>&#8220;Bunny tails&#8221; typically refer to a type of ornamental grass known scientifically as <strong>Lagurus ovatus</strong>. These charming plants are native to the Mediterranean region and are widely cultivated for their fluffy, soft flower heads that resemble the tails of rabbits, hence the name &#8220;bunny tails.&#8221;</p>



<p>Here are some key points about bunny tails:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Appearance</strong>: Bunny tails are known for their compact, upright growth habit and their flower heads, which are densely packed with tiny, soft bristles that look like miniature fluffy tails. The color of the flower heads can range from white to soft pink to light brown.</li>



<li><strong>Season and Growth</strong>: They are annual grasses, meaning they complete their life cycle in one season. They typically bloom in late spring to early summer and continue to provide interest through the summer months.</li>



<li><strong>Uses</strong>: They are popular in dried flower arrangements due to their unique texture and appearance. They can be harvested at their peak and dried upside down to preserve their fluffy flower heads. They add a whimsical touch to bouquets and floral crafts.</li>



<li><strong>Cultural Significance</strong>: In addition to their ornamental value in gardens and flower arrangements, bunny tails have cultural significance. They are often associated with innocence, playfulness, and the simple joys of nature, making them a favorite in floral design.</li>



<li><strong>Growing Conditions</strong>: These plants prefer full sun and well-drained soil. They are relatively easy to grow from seed and can be sown directly in the garden after the last frost date. They are drought-tolerant once established and generally low-maintenance.</li>
</ol>



<p>Overall, <a href="/products/">bunny tails</a> are beloved for their beauty and distinctive appearance, making them a delightful addition to gardens, floral displays, and decorative crafts.</p>



<p>Bunny tails, with their charming and whimsical appearance, can elevate your living space in several ways:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Natural Texture and Visual Appeal</strong>: The fluffy flower heads of bunny tails add a natural texture and visual interest to any room. Whether used fresh in a vase or dried in arrangements, they bring a touch of the outdoors inside, creating a warm and inviting atmosphere.</li>



<li><strong>Versatility in Decor</strong>: They are versatile and can complement various decor styles, from rustic and farmhouse to modern and minimalist. Their soft colors and delicate texture blend seamlessly with different color schemes and furnishings.</li>



<li><strong>Bringing Nature Indoors</strong>: Incorporating them into your decor allows you to bring a bit of nature indoors. They evoke a sense of tranquility and connection to the natural world, making your space feel more serene and relaxing.</li>



<li><strong>Seasonal Accent</strong>: Depending on how you use them, bunny tails can be a seasonal accent that changes with the time of year. Fresh bunny tails in spring and summer can brighten up your space, while dried bunny tails in fall and winter can add cozy warmth.</li>



<li><strong>DIY and Craft Projects</strong>: They are perfect for DIY projects and crafts. You can create stunning floral arrangements, wreaths, bouquets, and center pieces using fresh or dried bunny tails, allowing you to personalize your decor with handmade touches.</li>



<li><strong>Long-Lasting Beauty</strong>: <a href="/products/">Dried bunny tails</a> can last a long time without needing water or maintenance, making them a practical and sustainable decor choice. They retain their fluffy texture and colour, providing enduring beauty in your home.</li>
</ol>



<p>In summary, bunny tails are more than just decorative accents; they bring natural beauty, texture, and versatility to your living space, enhancing its aesthetic appeal and creating a cozy, inviting atmosphere for you and your guests to enjoy.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-left"><br>In addition to its ornamental value, this Grass is also used in dried flower arrangements and crafts. Its fluffy flower heads are long-lasting and can add a whimsical touch to any arrangement. July provides best quality<a href="https://www.riibaa.com/product-category/buy-pampas-in-nepal/best-bunny-tails-in-nepal/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"> bunny tails in Nepal.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/06/17/bunny-tails/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
